bestclassicbands.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy | The Best Classic Rock News, Features, Reviews + More

## Privacy Policy

Best Classic Bands operates the BestClassicBands.com website.

This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information for those that visit the site. Our Privacy Policy has been updated to reflect changes in data privacy laws, specifically the European Union’s (EU) General Data Protection Regulation ([ **GDPR**](https://www.eugdpr.org/)). These updates will take effect on May 25, 2018. By using our services on or after that date, you’ll be agreeing to these revisions. Best Classic Bands respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting it.

We reserve the right to update this Policy from time to time. If we do, we’ll let you know about any material changes by notifying you on this website.

If you choose to visit BestClassicBands.com, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection and Use**

For a better experience while using our service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, phone number, email address and postal address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is required and some is voluntary. For instance, our newsletter uses an opt-in form requiring your name and email address in order to subscribe. If you do not provide required information for a particular activity–such as a contest that requires you to provide your name, email address, and U.S. state of residence–you may not be permitted to participate in that activity. As noted in our contest rules, by participating, entrants grant permission for BestClassicBands.com and its contest partners to add them to their respective databases for future communication, such as a newsletter. These “subscribers” may unsubscribe or opt-out of this email list at any time.

**Log Data**

We want to inform you that whenever you visit this website, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages of our website that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Our website uses these “cookies” to collection information and to improve our service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our website. Most web browsers can be modified to decline cookies, though some portions of our website may thus not be able to be viewed by you.

**Service Providers**

We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

  * To facilitate our website and services;
  * To provide content and advertising to the website on our behalf;
  * To perform website-related services; or
  * To assist us in analyzing how our website is used.

We want to inform our website users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

**Security**

We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Best Classic Bands does not receive or store your credit card or bank account information.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our website may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services. If you are making a purchase via a third party on our website, such as offered by an advertiser, online retailer or ticket seller – though not limited to these examples – we strongly advise you to review the terms of use and privacy policies of the third party payment processor prior to  providing your information to them.

**Children’s Privacy**

Our website content does not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.

**Users in the European Union (EU)**

If you are a resident of the EU, you are entitled to the following rights once the GDPR becomes effective on May 25, 2018. In order to verify your identity, we may require you to provide us with personal information prior to accessing any records containing information about you.

You have the right to have your data erased from our services if the data is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was collected, you withdraw consent and no other legal basis for processing exists, or you believe your fundamental rights to data privacy and protection outweigh our legitimate interest in continuing the processing.

You have the right to restrict or object to our processing if we are processing your data based on legitimate interests or the performance of a task in the public interest as an exercise of official authority (including profiling); using your data for direct marketing (including profiling); or processing your data for purposes of scientific or historical research and statistics.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at info[at]bestclassicbands[dot]com.
